

# Dzikri Amrulloh

Administration & Creative Services Production

- **(**+62) 813-2495-9098
- ★ dzikriamrulloh.github.io
- Bandung, Indonesia

# SUMMARY

It is a source of pride for me to have the experience of being a Santri and handling various projects such as creative agency, visual management, and other projects. In this role, I developed innovative strategies, managed teams, and ensured the success of the projects. I also have experience in client communication, team coordination, and project budget management. I possess skills in project management, visual design, and organized event planning. Combining religious education and professional experience in the creative field gives me an advantage in facing various challenges and making positive contributions. More details about my experience and work, can be found on my portfolio website.

## EXPERIENCE

Internship Legal Officer 02/2024 - Present

**HHM Law Office** 

 Assisting in Auditing Case Data | Making Warning Letters (Somasi) | Making Legal Opinions | Attending Meetings Either With Clients Or Certain Parties | Assisting Office Mobility In Handling Cases.

# Internship (Jabar Innovation Fellowship)

07/2023 - 01/2024

Bureau of Law and Human Rights, Secretariat of the Regional Government of West Java 7 Province

 Managing the Database of Documentation of Regulations on Provincial Jdih, Managing Internal and External Events, Being a Host, Managing Media for Event Visualization Needs, Being an Event Documenter, and Assisting in Social Media Processing.

# Freelance Graphic Designer

02/2019 - 08/2024

Partnership

- Creating and Implementing Visual Graphics in Various Media, Both Print and Non-Print.
- Clients: PPM Al-Mu'awanah, HHM Law Office, Legal and Human Rights Bureau of the West Java Regional Secretariat, Youth and Sports Office of West Java Province, Several UMKNs, and Others

## Freelance VJ Mapping Show

02/2019 - 08/2024

Partnership

- Creating and Implementing VJ Animation for Event Backgrounds.
- Clients: PPM Al-Mu'awanah, PPM Darussalam Garut (Male & Female), PPM Robithoh, PPM Dampasan Banjarsari, PPM Darul Huda Banjar, Ponpes Daarul Ihsan (Cimahi & Banjaran) & PPM Baitussalam.

## Secretary to the Head of the Islamic boarding school

06/2021 - 05/2023

Al-Mu'awanah Modern Islamic Boarding School 7

Managing the Database of Each Section of the Boarding School. Managing Institutional Archives, Creating a Student
Assessment System, Digitizing Institutional Archives, Arranging Operational Standards for Several Sections of the Boarding
School, Arranging Correspondence for Both Institutions in Foundations and or Boarding Schools

# Web Developer & Studio Manager

11/2019 - 05/2023

Al-Mu'awanah Modern Islamic Boarding School 7

- Designing and Providing the Required Assets and Preparing Media Tools in the Capacity of Their Needs.
- · Creating and Designing Website Schemes.
- · Becoming a Visual Media Operator, Live Streaming, and others.

1/2

#### 08/2021 - 12/2022

# Freelance Graphic Designer

Imam Muda Salman ITB 7

• Managing Instagram Post Designs and Event Needs Designs.

**Photo Editor** 07/2019 - 11/2019

Newbrain Studio

• Manage and process photo results using Adobe Photoshop software.

## Language Management Staff

06/2018 - 07/2019

Al-Mu'awanah Modern Islamic Boarding School 7

 Controlling and Recording the Development of the Language of Students in the Al-Mu'awanah Modern Islamic Boarding School Environment.

### EDUCATION

#### Comparison of Madzhab and Law

2020 - 2024

Univertas Islam Negeri Sunan Gunung Djati Bandung - Bachelor's Degree (GPA 3.72)

- Awardee Jabar Innovation Fellowship 2023
- 1st Place in the Video Challenge Competition for the West Java OPD Category
- Completing Training Santri Siap Guna 39 Daarut Tauhid
- Completing Training Creative Thinking & Problem Solving by KEMENPORA
- · Purwakarta Religious Court Internship Participant

**Social Science** 2012 - 2018

Pondok Pesantren Modern Al-Mu'awanah - Middle School - High School

- 1st Place in the PORSENI English Speech Contest for all Sub-Districts
- · 1st Place in the PORSENI English Speech Contest for all Districts
- 2nd Place Speech FASI IX Majalaya Regional Coordinator
- 1st Place Islamic Story FASI IX Majalaya Regional Coordinator

#### SKILLS

Drone Pilot Intermediate Microsoft Office Advanced **Corel Draw** Advanced Adobe Photoshop Advanced Photography Intermediate Adoeb Illustrator Advanced Videography Intermediate **Creative Direction** Intermediate Adobe Premiere Pro Intermediate **Brand Consistency** Advanced UI/UX Intermediate Collaborative Skills Intermediate Figma Designer Advanced Communication Advanced Canva Designer Advanced Project Management Advanced Wordpress Intermediate Driving Car (SIM A) Advanced Intermediate Legal Analyzer - Civil Law Driving Motorcycle (SIM C) Advanced

#### LANGUAGES

Sundanese Native English Intermediate
Bahasa Native Arabic Intermediate